James D. Kim

- Diamond Bar, CA CELL (909) 342-0400 E-MAIL bronze10000@gmail.com
- PORTFOLIO https://bronze10000.github.io/portfolio/

PROFILE

As a full-stack web developer with a background in research and eCommerce, I bring my love of learning and an analytical mindset honed from conducting experiments on a lab bench. My ultimate goal is to continually improve my craft as a web developer by exploring new technologies and interweave them with awesome code.

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive

General Assembly

1933 S. Broadway, Los Angeles, CA 90007

B.S. in Botany

University of California, Davis 1 Shields Ave, Davis, CA 95616

SKILLS

HTML & CSS	Javascript	Ruby	Liquid
PHP	Ruby on Rails	Bootstrap	JQuery
MongoDB	MySQL	Git	ZenCart
Wordpress	Shopify	SEO	Ecommerce
Ebay	SASS	WooCommerce	

EXPERIENCE

Entrepreneur at BNJ Abrasives

Dec. 2017 - 2018

- Created a WooCommerce storefront for eCommerce business (<u>bnjabrasives.com</u>)
 Contract web developer at The Joy Factory
 Nov., 2016-Nov., 2017
- Heavily modify company Shopify website (Liquid, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS)
- Modify company microsite (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)
- Search Engine Optimization of company web presence

Freelance web developer

since April, 2014

- Develop Wordpress websites (<u>paccomabrasives.com</u>)
- Develop Shopify websites (purplelydia.com)
- Develop Zencart websites

Tutor

Spring, 2015

- Teach bioinformatics
- Explain current research in caloric restriction of yeast
- Use R Packages to conduct bioinformatics research using available datasets

Researcher

Spring, 2012-2014

• Studied role of Ecdysone Receptor, isoform A, in Aedes aegypti mosquito

Research Specialist

2005-2012(Spring)

• Studied G-protein signaling in filamentous fungus, Neurospora crassa

REFERENCES

Available upon request